securitywonks.net 2013-12-15

# SecurityWonks.netDownload Free and Open Source Software -

Introduction

We are committed to fair information practices and we respect the privacy and security of our users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from other users, and we may also ask you for personal information that enables us to give you access to some parts of our web site. We will not disclose your information to any person outside our organisation except as described in this Privacy Policy.

To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing our privacy practices. This statement describes what personal identifying information is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collected By Us

We collect certain information from and about our visitors in three ways: from our web server logs, by means of cookies, and directly from you.

_Web server logs_. When you visit our Web sites, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include your internet protocol address, what kind of browser or computer you use, the number of links you click within the site, the state or country from which you accessed the site, the date and time of your visit, the name of your internet services provider, the last page you viewed before visiting our site, and the pages you viewed on the site.

_Cookies_. If your browser allows it, our web sites use cookies, which are small text files which you computer creates or modifies on instruction of the page opened in your browser. These are used to save your preferences and login information. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Incase, if you choose to reject cookies, then, you may not be allowed access to privileged areas of the website.

_Information from you_. Visitors can register to obtain access to some parts of our web site. When you register, we will ask you for some personal information. Some of the information requested will be required for registration, and some may be optional. Also, we may ask you to disclose personal information to enable us to provide assistance and information to you.

Use Of And Access To Information

_Security and confidentiality of Collected Information_. We use technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control and information about our subscribers and their web site usage is maintained in a secure environment. Information about our subscribers and their web site usage is not shared with third parties for marketing purposes. We do not disclose any information about any subscriber's usage of our web site except in specific cases, and we do not share information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes unless you expressly give us permission to do so.

_Personally Identifiable information_. We will share your personal data as required by law or by the order of any competent court or (semi-)governmental authority or in matters of public safety or policy. Under strict conditions of confidentiality we may share your personal data with agents and contractors who use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us. We will also share your personal data as may be needed in connection with the enforcement of agreements.

_Anonymous information_. We may provide summary statistics about our interests and preferences of visitors of our web site, traffic patterns and related site information. These statistics do not include personally identifiable information.

Other Information Supplied By You

In some parts of our web site (such as Downloads section, support forums, weblinks, news submission etc) you can submit or contribute information. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Don't disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential.

Note: Support Forums, weblinks and news submission system will be available soon as we progress but for now, only Download section will be made available on the website.

Promotional Messages

You will not receive any promotional messages from us unless you opted to recieve them from us. If you don't want to receive promotional materials from us, you can opt out at any time. You can unsubscribe to topics in discussion forums, likewise in newsletter to stop recieving information on the site.

Note: Newsletter feature is in the works, we will give all standard opting out options (about recieving promotional materials), while we require you to accept this website related updates and announcements newsletter periodically, which helps you to utilise and enhance your user experience on the website.

Advertising Information

We were working with some advertising agencies like Google Adsense, CommissionJunction, Kontera and Product Companies like Reimage when showing non-intrusive plain leaderboard, skyscraper and square adverts and text link based adverts. They use cookies to track anonymous statistics as part of ad delivery and their privacy practices will be based on their individual privacy policies which follows:

Updates And Corrections

You can update your site account password with us, yourself, by logging into site, likewise, software publishers can update their software listings themselves anytime, last but not least, you can change different information in forums (that get displayed in forum profile).

Note: discussion forums will be available soon

Privacy Policy Changes

If there were any major update in our information practices, we will update that here and you can see the updates online soon after the updates are placed online in the website.

_This privacy policy was initially updated on 26 November 2007 and later had updates on 28 January 2010 and recent update on 14 Jan 2010._
